tuvie.com 2019-06-26

# Privacy Policy - Tuvie

The [http://www.tuvie.com](http://www.tuvie.com/) Privacy Statement

What follows is the Privacy Statement for all [http://www.tuvie.com](http://www.tuvie.com/) websites (a.k.a. blogs) including all the websites run under the [http://www.tuvie.com](http://www.tuvie.com/) domain.

Please read this statement regarding our blogs. If you have questions please ask us via our [contact form](http://www.tuvie.com/contact-us/).

This Privacy Policy applies to you as a reader, a contributor, a writer of content on our website, as a subscriber to our website, as a supplier to our business, as a contractor and in some circumstances as an employee.

In addition, for each visitor to our website cookies will be used which do not collect or disclose any Personal Information about the visitor, but do over time build up data regarding the visitor’s usage of our website.

**Email Addresses**

You may choose to add your email address to our contact list via the forms on our websites. We agree that we will never share you email with any third party and that we will remove your email at your request. We don’t currently send advertising via email, but in the future our email may contain advertisements and we may send dedicated email messages from our advertisers without revealing your email addresses to them. If you have any problem removing your email address please contact us via our contact form.

We also collect other data which may be included within the definition “personal data” for the purposes of the GDPR. This data collection might be done through several ways: subscribe to our site, contact us via email/phone, your business card, or any other document containing your personal information. We might also get your data when you visit our Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, or any other social media sites established by Tuvie.

**Ownership of Information**

We aspire to do the right, ethical and legal thing in bringing you this site, and we ask that you use the same judgment as you read, use, link to, and share the content hosted on Tuvie. When utilizing Tuvie content, we ask that you give credit where appropriate and don’t edit our content – or content that belongs to others without permission.

**Comments/Message Boards**

Most [http://www.tuvie.com](http://www.tuvie.com/) websites contain comment sections (a.k.a. message boards). We do not actively monitor these comments and the information on them is for entertainment purposes only. If we are alerted to something we deem inappropriate in any way, we may delete it at our discretion. We use email validation on most of our message boards in order to reduce “comment spam.” These email addresses will not be shared with any third party.

**Cookies**

Currently we assign cookies to our readers in order to save their preferences. This data is not shared with any third party. Accessing our websites is not dependent on accepting cookies and all major browsers allow you to disable cookies if you wish. These tracking technologies such as cookies do not personally identify you. If you do not wish to receive any cookies, you may set your browser to refuse them. However, your use of our website may be affected. 

**Third Party Cookies**

Many of our advertisers use cookies in order to determine the number of times you have seen an advertisement. This is done to limit the number times you are shown the same advertisement. [http://www.tuvie.com](http://www.tuvie.com/) does not have access to this data.

**About Google as Third Party Vendor**  
– Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
– Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
– Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**Traffic Reports**

Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular.

**Legal proceedings**

We will make every effort to preserve user privacy but [http://www.tuvie.com](http://www.tuvie.com/) may need to disclose information when required by law.

**Business Transitions**

If [http://www.tuvie.com](http://www.tuvie.com/) is acquired by or merges with another firm, the assets of our websites, including personal information, will likely be transferred to the new firm.

**Links**

[http://www.tuvie.com](http://www.tuvie.com/) website frequently link to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site’s privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by [http://www.tuvie.com](http://www.tuvie.com/)

**Notification of Changes**

When [http://www.tuvie.com](http://www.tuvie.com/) makes changes to this privacy policy we will post those changes here.

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
